♪No matter how far the road is, don’t be afraid♪
♪길이 아무리 멀더라도 두려워하지 마세요♪
♪Love is gentle and caring♪
♪사랑은 부드럽고 배려심이 깊습니다♪
♪Those wounds will definitely scab over♪
♪그 상처는 반드시 딱지가 될 거야♪
♪Everything gathers into the flower of time♪
♪모든 것은 시간의 꽃으로 모인다♪
♪ Someone will pick it up for you eventually ♪
♪결국 누군가가 당신을 대신해 가져갈 거예요♪
♪Keep going, you won’t be alone♪
♪계속 가세요. 당신은 혼자가 아닐 거예요♪
♪Conversation with time♪
♪시간과 함께 이야기 나누기♪
♪The light falls gently, just take it as her answer♪
♪빛이 살며시 내리는 걸 그녀의 대답이라고 생각해♪
♪May you have him in the sea of ​​people♪
♪그를 사람들의 바다 속에 두시기를 바랍니다 ♪
♪Live a simple and peaceful life♪
♪ 간단하고 평화로운 삶을 살아보세요♪
♪Understand that life is full of regrets♪
♪인생은 후회로 가득 차 있다는 것을 이해하세요♪
♪But, you still love♪
♪하지만 당신은 여전히 ​​사랑해요♪
♪This winter and summer♪
♪이번 겨울과 여름♪
[Love is the panacea] [Episode 3]
[사랑은 만병통치약] [3화]
[2022 Sichuan Province Characteristic Support Artworks]
[ 2022년 쓰촨성 지원 예술 작품 소개 ]
[Diadaptasi dari novel "Zhi Yu Zhe" karya Ning Meng Xi Yan]
[Diadaptasi dari 소설 "Zhi Yu Zhe" karya Ning Meng Xi Yan]
Saquon.
사쿤.
Very interesting, isn't it?
재미있지 않나요?
this.
이것.
For you.
당신을 위한.
Yeah.
유모.
What did you call me?
나한테 뭐라고 전화했어?
Saquon.
사쿤.
Release Dr. Gu.
구박사를 풀어주세요.
Do you have a tactile disorder?
촉각 장애가 있나요?
Don't like people touching you.
다른 사람이 당신을 만지는 것을 좋아하지 마십시오.
You talk to Saquon first.
먼저 사쿤에게 말을 걸어보세요.
Tell him I want to see him.
내가 그를 확인하고 싶다고 전해주세요.
Dad, make money.
아빠, 돈 벌어보세요.
Change?
돈을 찾고 계십니까?
Did you teach him?
당신이 그 사람을 가르쳤나요?
so small,
매우 작은,
But the origin of calling people father and mother.
그러나 아버지와 어머니로 사람을 부르는 유래 .
Did you teach him to slander and cheat money?
그에게 비방 하고 돈을 속이는 법을 가르쳤습니까?
What's the slander?
무엇을 비방?
Growing up, no one liked Saquon.
어린 시절부터 아무도 Sakun을 사랑하지 않았습니다.
good guy for him
그 사람에겐 좋은 사람
Will he call mom and dad?
그가 아버지와 어머니를 부를 것인가?
Such a small child
이런 작은 아이
Already tainted by your madness for money.
돈에 대한 당신의 광기로 오염되었습니다 .
So what if you need change?
그렇다면 돈을 찾고 있다면 어떨까요?
There is new money to treat disease.
질병을 치료할 수 있는 새로운 돈이 있습니다.
Sa Kun, please obey me.
사쿤, 복종해라.
No.
아니요.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
He is afraid of injections and medicine.
그는 주사와 약 복용을 두려워합니다.
Little real man.
작은 진짜 남자.
You listen to your uncle.
삼촌 잘 들어요.
now you
이제 당신은
I have to endure taking medicine every day .
매일 약을 먹어야 한다 .
even though you are sick
당신의 질병에도 불구하고
There is no cure now
지금은 치료가 불가능해요
perhaps
아마도
tomorrow or next year
내일 아니면 내년에
Effective drugs will appear
효과적인 약이 나타날 것이다
or new treatments.
또는 새로운 치료 방법.
so,
그래서,
now you have to survive
이제 살아남아야 해
and receive treatment.
그리고 치료를 받으세요.
( Can all diseases really be cured?)
(모든 질병은 정말 치료될 수 있을까?)
In fact, there are many more uncles and aunties
사실 삼촌, 이모들이 많아요
People who are surviving, struggling, trying.
살아남고, 고군분투하고, 열심히 노력하고 있는 사람 .
So, you can't give up.
그러니 포기할 수는 없습니다.
You still have to fight on your own
너도 스스로 싸워야 해
and survive.
그리고 살아남아라.
enthusiasm!
열광!
Could you please translate what I just said?
내가 방금 말한 것을 당신이 번역해 주네요
To Saquon.
사쿤에게.
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Let's translate it.
번역해 봅시다.
Saquon.
사쿤.
Let Dr. Gu check you out.
구 박사님께 진찰을 받아 보세요.
How about I take you out to play after I check it out ?
확인하고 나면 데리고 놀러 갈 테니 어때요?
I want to drink Coke.
나는 콜라를 마시고 싶다.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
lie.
누워.
I said a lot before
아까도 말을 너무 많이 했는데,
Did you only translate a sentence or two?
한두 문장만 번역하셨나요 ?
You are so talkative to find out.
당신은 너무 말이 많아요. 확인 해봐.
very good.
매우 좋은.
Saquon.
사쿤.
Once your head stops hurting
일단 머리가 안 아프면
Uncle will buy you a Coke.
삼촌이 콜라를 사줄게.
Thos.
토스.
Mother An, come up quickly.
안어머니, 빨리 오세요.
let's go.
갑시다.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
I don't want any more rumors to spread.
더 이상 루머가 퍼지는 것을 원하지 않습니다 .
I don't want to either.
나도 그러고 싶지 않아요.
I didn’t want to, but you agreed and Sakun took him to play.
원하지 않았지만 Sakun에게 그를 데려가겠다고 약속했습니다.
He is very obedient
그는 매우 순종적이다
and want to participate in therapy.
치료에 참여하고 싶습니다.
I can't break a promise to such a young child.
이렇게 어린 아이와의 약속을 어길 수는 없어요 .
There are many children who are unwilling to participate in therapy.
치료에 참여하기를 원하지 않는 아이들이 많이 있습니다 .
So, do you meet all the criteria?
그럼 조건을 다 충족하겠어요?
They suggest?
그들이 제안한다고?
After the operation is completed,
수술이 완료된 후,
His mother never visited him in the hospital.
그의 어머니는 한 번도 그를 병원에 방문한 적이 없습니다 .
He's still so little.
그는 아직 너무 작습니다.
he must be lonely
그 사람 정말 외로울 텐데
Very sad.
그리고 매우 슬프다.
That's why you're so special to Saquon.
그래서 당신은 Sakun을 특별하게 대합니다.
Because you feel sorry that his mother didn't come to visit him?
그의 어머니가 그를 찾아오지 않는 것이 안타깝기 때문입니까 ?
There are not so many reasons.
이유가 너무 많은 곳.
You are also special to Sakun .
당신은 또한 Sakun을 특별하게 대합니다.
So, what is your reason?
그렇다면 이유가 무엇인가요?
There are not so many reasons.
이유가 너무 많은 곳.
Saquon.
사쿤.
Dr. Gu is very busy.
구 박사님은 매우 바빠요.
He will stay with you all day today.
오늘 그는 하루 종일 당신과 동행해야 합니다.
You will become rich.
당신은 부자가 될 것입니다.
so.
그래서.
Make money.
돈을 벌다.
let's go.
갑시다.
This is luxury food
명품음식이네요
Did you say you wanted to eat that?
그거 먹고 싶다고 했어?
correct.
옳은.
This is the most famous culinary center of La Kaya.
이것은 Lacaya에서 가장 유명한 요리 센터입니다.
All available, all sold.
모두 가능하며 모두 판매되었습니다.
Plus, everything is edible.
게다가 모든 것이 먹을 수 있습니다.
slowly.
느리게.
Ann's mother.
안의 어머니.
There's popcorn here.
여기 팝콘이 있어요.
Do you want to eat?
먹을 래?
want to.
고 싶어요.
Make me pay for this.
비용은 제가 지불하겠습니다.
careful.
조심해.
Half of the exam time has passed.
시험시간이 반이 지났습니다.
The only thing I can do is not come to the exam.
시험에 오지 않는 것으로 간주 될 수 있습니다.
Take the make-up exam next month.
다음 달에 교정 시험을 치르세요.
There is no remedial testing.
교정 테스트가 없습니다.
Must rank in the top three for eight consecutive years
8년 동안 상위 3위 안에 들어야 함
This will give you a chance to enter Huaren Hospital.
화렌병원에 들어갈 기회가 생기도록 말이죠.
I didn't mean to be late.
일부러 늦은 건 아니었어요.
I take patients to the hospital.
나는 아픈 사람들을 병원에 데려갑니다.
Taking patients to the hospital?
아픈 사람을 병원에 데려가나요?
correct.
옳은.
Can anyone prove it?
증명할 수 있는 사람이 있나요?
(I'll prove it.)
(증명하겠습니다.)
(He was late because)
(그가 늦었기 때문에)
(Rescue patients suffering from epilepsy.)
( 갑자기 간질이 생긴 환자 구하기)
(So, he missed the exam time.)
(그래서 그는 시험 시간을 놓쳤습니다.)
♪Who doesn’t feel lost in confusion? ♪
♪혼란 속에서 길을 잃지 않는 사람은 누구일까요 ?♪
♪Find one among billions of possibilities♪
♪ 수억 개의 가능성 중 하나를 찾아서 ♪
♪Trapped in a city called destiny ♪
♪운명이라는 도시에 갇혀 ♪
Saquon.
사쿤.
Are you OK?
당신은 괜찮죠?
Thank you, Teacher Gu.
감사합니다, 구 선생님.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Why when doing everything
다 할 때 왜
Like you're risking your life?
목숨을 걸고 있는 것처럼요?
Before caring about others,
남을 배려하기 전에
Can you take care of yourself first?
먼저 자신을 잘 돌볼 수 있나요 ?
Individualistic heroism.
개인주의적 영웅주의.
No one told you that you are handsome?
누구도 당신에게 당신이 아주 잘생겼다고 말한 적이 없나요?
When you don't talk?
말 안 할 때?
Saquon.
사쿤.
Don't run.
실행되지 않습니다.
This is for you.
이건 널위한거야.
What's this?
이건 뭐죠?
This is
이것은
The most famous dish here is the high-protein croquettes .
이곳에서 가장 유명한 고단백 튀김 미트볼 .
Crispy and delicious.
바삭하고 맛있습니다.
High protein croquettes?
고단백 튀김 미트볼?
I eat, yes.
나는 먹는다, 응.
Eat it.
그것을 먹을.
Share the good luck.
행운을 나눠보세요.
you eat.
먹어.
- This is for you to eat. - you eat.
- 이건 네가 먹을 거야. - 먹어.
you eat.
먹어.
you eat first.
당신이 먼저 먹어요.
Exploding spiders.
튀긴 거미.
It was so delicious.
너무 맛있었습니다.
Your fish is cooked.
생선이 요리되었습니다.
I told you, eat it.
내가 말했잖아, 넌 먹어.
Uh...what's wrong?
여... 무슨 일이야?
There are ashes.
재가 있습니다.
Father, mother and child.
아버지, 어머니, 아이.
we are not...
우리는하지 않습니다...
Dad, I want to eat fish.
아빠, 저는 생선을 먹고 싶어요.
I want to eat fish.
나는 생선을 먹고 싶다.
Saquon.
사쿤.
What are you doing ? You can't call it at will.
뭐하세요 임의로 호출할 수 없습니다.
I won't be fooled by you.
나는 당신에게 속지 않을 것입니다.
Take your time, Saquon.
천천히, 사쿤.
Saquon.
사쿤.
Let me check.
내가 체크해 볼게.
bad.
나쁜.
Poor blood clotting.
혈액 응고가 좋지 않습니다.
Once it bleeds, it cannot be stopped.
한번 피가 나면 멈출 수가 없습니다.
Wear a shirt to hold it up.
그것을 들어 올리려면 셔츠를 입으십시오.
Stop bleeding
피를 흘리지 마십시오.
Don't be afraid, Saquon.
두려워하지 마세요, 사쿤.
Mali.
마리.
careful.
조심해.
HIV positive.
HIV 양성.
Needs sewing.
바느질이 필요합니다.
Be prepared for protection.
보호를 준비하십시오.
Okay, I'm going to disinfect it.
알겠습니다. 소독하겠습니다.
Come on, let me put it on for you.
어서, 입는 걸 도와줄게.
Wear another set.
다른 세트를 착용하십시오.
I start.
나는 시작한다.
[How to help your best friend conquer the girl of your dreams? 】
[가장 친한 친구가 꿈의 남자를 이길 수 있도록 돕는 방법은 무엇입니까?]
power cut?
정전?
Dr. Zhang.
장 박사.
You just scared me!
당신은 나를 놀라게 했어요!
Jiang, it’s me.
장, 나야.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
There's a power outage, why did you go out?
정전이 됐는데 왜 그냥 나가나요?
I happened to be writing a thesis.
마침 논문을 쓰고 있거든요.
The oil lamp also went out.
기름불도 나갔습니다.
The power was out, so I went outside to get some fresh air.
정전이 되어 바깥 공기를 좀 쐬러 나갔습니다.
you...
너...
Why are you alone?
왜 혼자예요?
Di mana Su Wei'an?
디마나 수웨이안?
I didn't see him all day today.
오늘 나는 하루 종일 그를 보지 못했습니다.
When I called him, his words were slurred.
그를 부를 때 그의 말 역시 모호했다.
I don't know what he did.
나는 그가 무엇을 했는지 모른다.
Must be looking for money.
돈을 찾고 있어야합니다.
What can he do?
그는 무엇을 할 수 있나요?
What matters is that the call is connected.
중요한 것은 통화가 연결된다는 점이다.
Have you not graduated with a master's degree and are already working?
당신은 석사 졸업 하고 이미 일하고 있지 않습니까?
Why are you still writing your thesis?
왜 아직도 논문을 쓰고 있나요?
Academician Qiu Fazu once said,
Qiu Fazu 학자는 이렇게 말했습니다.
People who only know how to operate
운영만 할 수 있는 사람들
Refers to operating technicians.
운영 기술자를 의미합니다.
Medicine must master clinical practice and scientific research.
의학은 임상 실습과 과학적 연구를 마스터해야 합니다 .
Besides, following Boss these past few years,
게다가 몇 년 동안 보스를 따라다닌 끝에
I feel more and more that what the boss said is right.
나는 점점 보스의 말이 옳다는 것을 느낀다.
Scientific research ability affects clinical practice thinking.
과학적 연구 역량은 임상 실습에서의 사고에 영향을 미칩니다.
If you want to realize your dream of medicine, you must learn throughout your life.
의학적 꿈을 실현하려면 평생 공부해야 합니다.
Why...are you looking at me like this?
왜... 나를 그렇게 보는 거야?
I envy you.
나는 당신이 질투합니다.
it is true.
그건 진실이야.
Those who have dreams will definitely shine.
꿈이 있는 사람은 빛날 것이다.
If you keep your word, everyone will shine.
당신의 말에 순종하면 모든 사람이 빛날 것입니다.
Who doesn’t have dreams?
꿈이 없는 사람이 어디 있겠는가?
I have no dreams.
나는 꿈이 없습니다.
I used to be a follower of Vian.
나는 Wei'an의 추종자였습니다.
Wherever he goes, I go.
나는 그가 가는 곳이면 어디든 갑니다.
He is very good at learning.
그는 공부를 아주 잘해요.
A little whip cracks every day to push me forward.
매일 나를 계속 나아가게 만드는 작은 채찍이 휘두릅니다.
So, me too
그럼 나도
Go to a pretty good college.
꽤 좋은 대학에 가세요.
He likes to study medicine,
그는 의학 공부를 좋아하고,
I also studied medicine with him.
나도 그와 함께 의학을 공부하러 갔다.
But I studied zoology, which is very different from him.
하지만 나는 그와 매우 다른 동물학을 공부했습니다.
Not really.
설마.
Very.
매우.
Then,
그 다음에,
He studied French.
그는 프랑스어를 공부했어요.
I also researched it.
나도 조금 공부했다.
However, my French is not as good as his.
하지만 내 프랑스어는 그 사람만큼 좋지 않아요.
after that,
이후,
he suddenly said
그가 갑자기 말했다
He wants to study in France,
그 사람은 프랑스로 유학 가고 싶어해요.
go to paris
파리로 가다
I'm serious this time
이번엔 진심이야
I can no longer accompany him.
더 이상 그 사람과 함께 갈 수 없어요.
when i found out
내가 알았을 때
If Wei An really didn’t go to Paris
웨이안이 실제로 파리에 가지 않았다면
And also dropped out of school.
그리고 학교도 그만뒀다.
He gave up on the dream he had held on to for so long.
그는 오랫동안 품고 있던 꿈을 포기했다 .
I was completely panicked.
나는 완전히 당황했다.
Even Wei An was willing to give up.
Wei'an조차도 기꺼이 포기했습니다.
What should I do?
그러면 어떻게 해야 합니까?
Do you think I'm disappointed?
내가 매우 실망했다고 생각하나요?
No.
아니요.
Life is so long.
인생은 너무 깁니다.
One day you won't just follow.
언젠가는 더 이상 따라만 하지 않게 될 날이 올 것입니다.
You'll know what you want to do.
당신은 당신이 무엇을하고 싶은지 알게 될 것입니다 .
However, what makes me panic
그런데 나를 당황하게 만든 것은
It's that I don't know what I can do.
내가 무엇을 할 수 있는지 모른다는 것입니다 .
Everyone has their own skills
사람은 누구나 자신만의 기술을 가지고 있다
and preferred areas.
그리고 선호하는 분야.
It's just a matter of time.
그것은 모두 시간 문제일 뿐입니다.
For example, although Su Weian is very smart,
예를 들어 Su Wei'an은 매우 똑똑하지만
I think
나는 느낀다
You have advantages that he doesn't have.
당신에게는 그 사람이 갖지 못한 장점도 있습니다 .
What are the advantages?
어떤 장점이 있나요?
Try saying it.
말해 보세요.
You are good to your friends.
당신은 친구에게 매우 좋은 사람입니다.
What are the benefits of doing this?
이것의 장점은 무엇입니까?
I guess what you would say.
무슨 말을 하려는 것 같군요.
Of course this is an advantage.
물론 이것은 장점이다.
There are many people who are friendly to their friends.
친구한테 친절하게 대해주는 사람이 너무 많아요 .
However, only a few people
그러나 소수의 사람들만이
He puts the interests of his friends before his own.
자기 친구보다 친구의 이익을 먼저 생각하는 사람 .
I remember your eyes were already red that day.
그날 당신의 눈은 이미 빨개졌던 것을 기억합니다.
You still don't give up on the Boss.
당신은 아직도 보스를 포기하지 않습니다.
You forced me
강요한 건 너야
Go to the police station to save Su Wei'an
소웨이안을 구하기 위해 경찰서에 갔다
Very cool.
아주 멋지다.
In addition, I think Su Weian is also very lucky.
게다가 Su Wei'an 도 매우 행운아라고 생각합니다.
Because he has a friend like you.
그 사람에게도 너 같은 친구가 있으니까.
Your words almost made me cry.
당신의 말은 나를 거의 울게 만들었습니다.
OK
좋아요.
So, starting from today,
그럼 오늘부터,
In my friends list,
내 친구 목록에는
Added a male friend named Fang.
Fang이라는 남자 친구가 추가되었습니다 .
higher.
훨씬 더 높습니다.
More on the right.
오른쪽에 더 있습니다.
already.
이미.
you...
너...
Are you OK?
괜찮아요?
You tripped on a flat surface
평평한 표면에서 넘어졌습니다.
Because of ataxia?
운동실조 때문에?
Who suffers from ataxia?
운동실조증이 있는 사람은 누구입니까?
Hypoglycemia.
저혈당증.
Is it really possible?
정말 괜찮나요?
Are you OK?
어떻게 지내세요?
Check again to see if anyone is injured.
부상자가 있는지 다시 확인하세요.
Are you following me?
나에게 관심을 기울이고 있습니까?
No.
아니요.
Calm down.
진정해.
There are no wounds on my body.
몸에는 상처가 없어요.
We all have to take PEP medication.
우리 모두는 PEP 약을 복용해야 합니다.
I'm hungry.
나 배고파.
Ayo,
아요,
Let's go have a meal together
우리 같이 먹으러 가
Mali.
마리.
Taste it.
맛보세요.
Came late today
오늘은 늦었어,
This is the only thing in the cafeteria.
매점에는 이것밖에 없어요.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
What’s wrong with you?
당신에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
my father was
나의 아버지는 예전에
he also likes
그 사람도 그걸 좋아해
Top with two fried eggs.
그 위에 계란 후라이 두 개를 올려주세요.
Your father?
아버지?
so...
그래서...
Three years ago, he
3년 전 그는
Became a star in the sky.
하늘의 별이 되었습니다.
Is this the reason why you don't go to school?
학교를 그만둔 이유도 이것 때문이었나요?
of course not.
당연히 아니지.
It has nothing to do with my father.
아버지와는 아무 관련이 없습니다.
I just want to make money.
나는 단지 돈을 벌고 싶을 뿐이다.
Earn more money.
더 많은 돈을 벌어보세요.
There are many opportunities for Lakaya;
라카야에는 많은 기회가 있습니다.
Make money fast.
빨리 돈을 벌어.
Money comes from everywhere.
모든 곳이 돈의 원천입니다.
Besides, you don't know
게다가 넌 모르잖아
Europeans are very generous when it comes to giving
유럽인들은 기부에 매우 관대합니다.
There was no hesitation in tipping.
팁을 주고 조금도 주저하지 않았습니다.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Is it your family?
당신의 가족입니까?
Are you really short of money?
정말 돈이 부족해요?
Who would think that money is too much?
누가 돈이 너무 많다고 생각하겠습니까 ?
People who value money so much...
돈을 너무 중요하게 생각하는 사람들 ..
You can save people by postponing final exams.
사람들을 구하기 위해 학기말 시험을 연기할 수 있습니다 .
you can help others
당신은 사람들을 도울 수 있습니다
Almost considered a murderer.
거의 살인자로 간주됩니다.
Do you believe?
당신은 그것을 믿습니까?
Anyway, I don’t believe it.
어쨌든 나는 그것을 믿지 않습니다.
Make money while studying medicine
돈을 벌어 의학 공부를 하고,
I choose to make money.
나는 돈을 버는 것을 선택했다.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Did you make a lot of money in Lakaya?
라카야에서 돈을 많이 벌었나요 ?
So much so that it helps Saquon pay for his medical bills.
사쿤이 의료비를 지불하는 데 도움이 될 만큼 말이죠 .
I'm like, why are you so confused?
제 생각에는 왜 그렇게 혼란스러워요?
Guru teacher.
Guru Gu.
you...
너...
Do you support Darwin's theory of evolution?
다윈의 진화론을 지지하시나요 ?
Do you mean...
당신은 다음을 언급하고 있습니다 ...
Living things compete for survival,
생물들은 생존을 위해 경쟁하고,
The survival of the ruler.
통치자의 생존.
The defective gene must be removed naturally.
결함이 있는 유전자는 자연적으로 제거되어야 합니다.
I only believe
나는 단지 믿는다
About the Hippocratic Oath.
히포크라테스 선서에 대해.
Maintain respect and treatment wherever possible
가능한 한 존중과 대우를 유지하십시오.
For every life.
모든 생명을 위해, 평생을 위해.
so you
그래서 당신은
Never experienced a moment of despair
한 번도 절망의 순간을 경험한 적이 없다.
In what areas are the patients you are treating not getting better?
당신이 치료하고 있는 환자의 상태가 호전되지 않는 곳은 어디입니까?
We as doctors have no right to despair.
의사로서 우리는 절망할 권리가 없습니다.
us
우리
Must survive to the end.
끝까지 살아남아야 한다.
Can not give up.
포기할 수 없습니다.
All because of you.
그것은 모두 당신 때문이다.
Who asked you to chat with me for so long?
누가 나한테 그렇게 오래 얘기하자고 했어?
There is no one in the cafeteria now.
이제 식당에는 사람이 한 명도 없습니다 .
Who makes dinner?
저녁은 누가 만드나요?
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Can't let anyone see us together.
누구도 우리가 함께 있는 모습을 볼 수 없습니다 .
Why can't you just let nature take its course?
왜 그냥 놔두면 안 되나요?
Does anyone else see us together?
다른 사람들이 우리 같이 있는 걸 볼까?
Yes, why?
예, 왜요?
What are you guilty of?
당신은 무엇에 대해 죄책감을 느끼나요?
I've been hiding
나는 숨어 있었어,
Now that it's out, it's really weird.
이제 나왔으니 확실히 매우 이상합니다.
Not even a ghost.
유령도 한 명도 없었어요.
look.
바라보다.
There is a boss.
사장님이 한 분 계십니다.
boss.
보스.
Doctor Gu, why are you here too?
구 박사님, 당신도 여기에 왜 오셨나요?
I...I'm hungry.
나... 배고파요.
Who eats noodles with you?
누가 당신과 함께 국수를 먹나요?
Where is that person?
그 사람은 어디에 있나요?
nobody.
아무도.
only myself.
나만 혼자.
So why are there two bowls of noodles?
그럼 국수는 왜 두 그릇이 있는 걸까요?
I want to eat two bowls of noodles.
국수 두 그릇 먹고 싶어요.
Isn't it possible?
불가능합니까?
Have you used these two pairs of chopsticks ?
이 두 쌍의 젓가락은 이미 사용된 젓가락이죠?
I like
좋아요
A bowl and a pair of chopsticks.
한 그릇 과 한 쌍의 젓가락이 결합된 것입니다.
Isn't it possible?
가능하지 않나요?
able.
할 수 있다.
boss.
보스.
Where are you going today?
너는 오늘 어디 가니?
It seems this is the first time
이번이 처음인 것 같네요
Were you on vacation after coming here?
여기 오시고 휴가 중이시죠?
I haven't seen you all day, I'm so...
하루 종일 못 봤는데, 정말...
I'm not used to this.
나는 그것에 익숙하지 않습니다.
Me too.
저도요.
I didn't see Wei An all day.
나는 하루 종일 웨이안을 보지 못했습니다.
I'm not used to it either.
나도 익숙하지 않아요.
boss.
보스.
you...
여러분...
Why us?
우린 왜?
I'm not with Su Wei'an.
나는 Su Wei'an과 함께 있지 않습니다.
It’s rare to have an afternoon break
오후에 쉬는 경우가 거의 없는데,
So just take a walk.
그러니 그냥 산책을 하세요.
Boss, I didn’t ask you and Su to translate.
보스, 나도 당신과 수 번역가에게 묻지 않았습니다 .
Let me ask you and translator Jiang,
당신과 장 번역가에게 물었습니다.
Would you like to eat scallion pancakes or dumplings?
파전을 먹을래 아니면 만두를 먹을래 ?
I eat noodles.
나는 국수를 먹는다.
Take a seat, Jiang.
앉아라, 장쩌민.
I made scallion pancakes for you.
파 팬케이크를 만들어 줬어요.
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
Are you OK?
당신은 괜찮죠?
Why do I feel like you look nervous?
왜 당신이 매우 긴장한 것 같은 느낌이 들죠?
I...I'm not nervous.
나... 별로 긴장 안 됐어.
Am I nervous?
내가 긴장했나요?
No.
아니요.
good smell.
매우 향기로운.
Mari, cicipi. Jiang Muying.
마리, cicipi.Jiang Muying.
Scallion pancakes made by the aunt in the cafeteria
매점 이모가 만들어준 파전
very delicious.
아주 맛있는.
what time is it?
지금 몇 시지?
Why do you think Wei An hasn’t come home yet?
웨이안이 왜 아직 집에 돌아오지 않았다고 생각하세요 ?
Why haven't you gone home yet?
왜 아직도 집에 없나요?
You contact him.
당신은 그에게 연락합니다.
If you can't,
당신이 할 수 없다면,
I'll accompany you to pick him up.
그를 데리러 동행하겠습니다.
What is that sound?
무슨 소리야?
That's...my text message.
그건... 내 짧은 메시지야.
short message.
짧은 메시지.
It's hot.
너무 더워.
I am too careless.
나는 너무 부주의했다.
just me.
나만.
Not hot either.
또한 덥지도 않습니다.
My hands are relatively sensitive.
손이 더 예민해요.
Jiang Muying.
장무잉.
Su Wei'an is becoming more and more courageous, isn't he?
소웨이안의 배짱이 점점 커지고 있지 않나요?
You dare to go out alone at this time of night .
이 밤 시간에는 감히 혼자 나가기도 합니다.
Has General Kouyate's anger subsided?
쿠야트 장군의 분노가 가라앉았습니까?
so...
그래서...
bad.
나쁜.
The phone only rang once and then turned off, right?
핸드폰이 딱 한 번 울리고 꺼졌죠?
So, he couldn't have been captured by General Kouyate, right?
그렇다면 그는 Kuyat 장군에게 체포될 수 없었을 것입니다. 그렇죠?
cannot. I had to... I had to look for it.
캔트. 난... 그를 찾아야 해요.
Fang Mingfan.
팡밍판.
Jiang Muying went out alone at night
강무잉은 밤에 혼자 나갔다
Go find Su Wei'an.
Su Wei'an을 찾으러.
Lakaya is too dangerous
라카야는 너무 위험해요
Are you calm?
당신은 침착합니까?
Wait for me, Jiang.
기다려, 장.
Why do you want to scare Jiang?
왜 장쩌민을 겁주는 거야?
He really came out to me.
정말 저를 찾으러 나오셨어요.
If I don't kick him out
내가 그 사람을 쫓아내지 않으면,
Do you still have a chance to blame me now ?
지금 아직도 나를 비난할 기회가 있나요 ?
You call him quickly.
빨리 그 사람에게 전화하세요.
It can also call him back.
또한 그에게 다시 전화를 걸 수도 있습니다.
This is also true.
그것도 맞습니다.
Hello, Teacher Jiang.
안녕하세요 지앙님.
I...
나...
I am fine.
나는 괜찮아.
Just on the road
그냥 길에
Meet old customers
오래된 고객을 만나다
and had dinner with him. that's right.
그리고 그 사람과 저녁을 먹어요. 좋아요.
I'm back.
나는 돌아왔다.
Wait for me in the room.
방에서 기다려 주세요.
Until it was discovered.
발견될 때까지.
I go first.
내가 먼저 간다.
slowly.
느리게.
[Moutai buying price (official) 42,710 francs, selling price 100 US dollars/600 yuan]
[Moutai 구매 가격(공식) 42,710 프랑 판매 가격 100 US 달러/600 RMB]
[The first million dollar financial plan]
[ 최초 100만 달러 재정 계획 ]
[CITIC Bank interest rate 1.95; Shanghai Pudong Development Bank interest rate 1.55]
[CITIC 은행 이자율 1.95; SPD 은행 금리 1.55]
Why don't you look at other people's stuff carefully?
왜 남의 물건을 함부로 쳐다보나요?
I don't know whose it is.
나는 그것이 누구인지 모른다.
If you don't know who it is from , you shouldn't watch it.
누구인지 모르면 쳐다보지도 마세요.
Don't know whose it belongs to
누구인지는 모르겠지만,
So you have to look at who it actually belongs to
그래서 실제로 누구의 것인지 살펴봐야 합니다.
Return it to its owner.
주인에게 돌려주기 위해.
Then, what did you see?
그럼, 무엇을 보셨나요?
What did I see?
나는 무엇을 봅니까?
I see other people 's obsession with making money.
나는 다른 사람들이 돈을 벌려는 끈기를 봅니다.
And the ability to calculate everything.
또한 모든 것을 계산하는 능력도 있습니다 .
Before the age of 60,
60세 이전에는
He absolutely can
그 사람은 분명 그럴 수도 있지
A very wealthy money maniac.
돈이 아주 많은 부자.
Su Wei'an,
수웨이안,
I started to really believe it
나는 그것을 정말로 믿기 시작했다.
You would give up studying medicine to make money.
당신은 돈을 벌기 위해 의학 공부를 포기할 것입니다 .
only,
그건 그저,
The life of a man who gave up his dreams for money ,
돈을 위해 자신의 꿈을 포기한 사람의 삶 ,
Is it a bit weak?
좀 약한거 아냐?
Right in the operating room,
바로 수술실에서
You just hold up the light like this,
당신은 램프를 그렇게 들고 있어요.
At first glance I thought
얼핏 생각했다
You are one of our members.
당신은 우리 회원 중 하나입니다.
Su Wei'an, what are you thinking about?
Su Wei'an, 정확히 무슨 생각을 하고 있나요?
I remember when you saw the stars I said
네가 별을 봤을 때 내가 말했던 게 기억나
Starlight is so heartbreaking...
별빛이 너무 가슴 아프네요..
like the memories left behind
남겨진 추억처럼
The dead are in the hearts of the living.
산 자의 마음 속에 죽은 자 .
However, I think
그러나 나는 오히려 이렇게 생각했다.
Even if you are destined to die,
죽을 운명이라 할지라도
stars will stay
별은 남을 것이다
Devoted to his last labors,
마지막 수고를 하고 있다.
His last strength,
그의 마지막 힘,
Leave the brightest light in the dark sky.
어두운 하늘에 가장 밝은 빛을 남기기 위해 .
Just like every one of us.
우리 모두처럼.
Each of us is destined to die.
우리 각자는 죽을 운명입니다.
However, our values ​​exist in this world
하지만 우리의 가치관은 이 세상에 살아있습니다
Like the light of those stars,
저 별빛처럼
Can shine forever.
영원히 빛날 수 있습니다.
What Teacher Gu said is true.
구 선생님 말씀이 맞습니다.
However, maybe I will disappoint Master Gu.
하지만 아마도 구 선생님을 실망시켜야 할 것 같습니다.
Making money is my whole dream.
돈 버는 것이 내 꿈이다.
In addition, I also hope to borrow the blessing of Teacher Gu,
그 외에도 구 사부의 축복도 빌리고 싶습니다.
I can live to be 60 years old in frail condition.
60세까지는 약하게 살아갈 수 있다 .
Are you back already?
벌써 돌아오셨나요?
You must be very tired, right?
피곤하겠지?
Mali,
마리,
I'll give you a massage.
내가 마사지해줄게.
Mali.
마리.
What, this power?
어때, 이 힘?
Yes.
예.
Really comfortable.
정말 편안해요.
Come out and take me.
나와서 나를 데려가세요.
Too much?
너무 많은?
I can still help you share some of the burden.
나는 여전히 당신이 부담을 일부 나누도록 도울 수 있습니다.
This includes evening snacks.
여기에는 저녁 간식도 포함됩니다.
I know you moved me for no more than three seconds.
나는 당신이 나를 감동시킨 지 3초도 채 되지 않았다는 것을 압니다.
today,
오늘,
If I hadn’t met Dr. Gu in the cafeteria,
구내식당에서 구박사를 만나지 못한다면
I thought you two went out together.
둘이 같이 나간 줄 알았는데
how so?
어떻게 그럴수있어?
He doesn't like me, you know?
그 사람은 나를 좋아하지 않는 거 알지?
I have no idea.
모르겠습니다.
I even feel it
느껴지기도 해요
You are very capable of stimulating his emotions.
당신은 그의 감정을 자극하는 데 매우 능숙합니다.
Isn't this a special kind of existence?
이것은 특별한 존재가 아닌가 ?
include.
포함.
Very special.
매우 특별합니다.
This is really special.
정말 특별해요.
no.
아니다.
You didn't see him today.
오늘 당신은 그를 보지 못했습니다.
Tonight, he is
오늘 밤 그는
Looking so lonely and weak.
너무 외롭고 약해 보여요.
Looks very thirsty for love.
사랑에 목마른 것 같습니다.
Very.
매우.
why me...
왜 나야...
I mean,
내 말은,
How can you see it?
어떻게 볼 수 있나요?
very clear.
매우 명확한.
you think,
당신은 생각한다,
a normal adult man
평범한 성인남자
So cold and firm,
너무 차갑고 단단해서
In the cafeteria at midnight
자정에 구내식당에서
Cook two bowls of noodles.
국수 두 그릇을 요리하세요.
Still use two pairs of chopsticks.
아직도 두 쌍의 젓가락을 사용하고 있습니다.
It turns out
증명한다
He is waiting for the person to eat noodles with him.
그는 함께 국수를 먹고 있는 사람을 기다리고 있었습니다 .
Don't you feel it?
느껴지지 않나요?
Very sensitive?
아주 예민한데?
Is it moving?
움직이고 있나요?
Why do I feel so sick?
왜 이렇게 역겨운 느낌이 들까요?
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
You've learned to be stupid, haven't you?
바보가 될 때까지 공부했지, 그렇지?
I don’t understand the romance of life.
인생의 낭만을 이해하지 못합니다.
Jiang.
장.
Gu Yunzheng,
구윤정,
He is so great,
그는 정말 대단해요,
But still single.
하지만 계속 싱글이다.
do you think it's because
생각하니?
Didn't he find anyone to eat noodles with him?
국수를 먹으러 동행할 사람을 찾지 못했다 고요?
so...
그래서...
He's too arrogant
그 사람은 너무 거만해요.
In his eyes, apart from medicine
그의 눈에는 의학 외에
Absolutely nothing else.
다른 것은 전혀 없습니다.
Your words are exactly the same as Fang Mingfan's.
당신의 말은 Fang Mingfan과 똑같습니다 .
Fang Mingfan still said
Fang Mingfan은 여전히 ​​​​말했습니다.
Gu Yunzheng's partner is
구윤정의 파트너는
Cushing. You know that, right?
쿠싱. 아시죠?
What does this prove?
이것이 무엇을 증명합니까?
This proves that you know Gu Yunzheng very well.
이것은 당신이 Gu Yunzheng을 너무 많이 이해하고 있다는 것을 증명합니다.
You two weren't close, but you understood him.
두 사람은 친하지 않았지만 그를 이해했습니다.
perhaps
아마도
he is
그는
Is this special being waiting for you?
당신을 기다리고 있어요, 이 특별한 존재?
According to me.
나에 따라.
Jiang.
장.
Do you know what part of you I envy the most ?
내가 당신의 어떤 부분을 가장 부러워하는지 아세요 ?
What?
무엇?
I envy your rich imagination.
당신의 훌륭한 상상력이 부럽습니다.
I'll give you a start,
시작하겠습니다.
You can create something world-famous.
세계적으로 유명한 작품을 만들 수 있습니다 .
Doctor Gu, please save him.
구 박사님, 그를 구해주세요.
Translator Su has no money to pay the fine.
수 번역가는 스스로 벌금을 낼 돈이 없고 ,
But I have money to pay my neighbor’s medical bills.
하지만 이웃의 병원비를 지불할 돈이 있습니다 .
This neighbor is not simple, yes.
이 이웃은 단순하지 않습니다.
Did you make a lot of money in Lakaya?
라카야에서 돈을 많이 벌었나요 ?
So much so that it helps Saquon pay for his medical bills.
사쿤이 의료비를 지불하는 데 도움이 될 만큼 말이죠 .
Father, mother and child.
아버지, 어머니, 아이.
we are not...
우리는하지 않습니다...
Dad, I want to eat fish.
아빠, 저는 생선을 먹고 싶어요.
I want to eat fish.
나는 생선을 먹고 싶다.
Saquon.
사쿤.
What are you doing ? You can't call it at will.
뭐하세요 임의로 호출할 수 없습니다.
[Kota Jinhai, Farmasi Jiehui]
[코타 진하이, 파마시 지에후이]
Regular use of a brain pacemaker
뇌 박동 조율기 자주 사용
[CEO Du Yuncheng] used for neurodegenerative diseases.
[두윤청 대표] 신경퇴행성질환에 쓰인다.
including Parkinson's disease,
파킨슨병을 비롯해
Huntington's disease, etc.
헌팅턴병 등.
Is Wei An very busy recently?
웨이안은 요즘 바빴나요?
He hasn't been here for a month.
그는 한 달 동안 오지 않았습니다.
Pu Du.
박두.
Professor Wen called and said
원 교수가 전화해서 말했다.
You have not asked Finance to allocate project funds
재무팀 에 프로젝트 자금 이체를 요청하지 않았습니다.
It should be coming this month.
이번 달에 와야 할 것.
This HDQ39 project
이 HDQ39 프로젝트
We have been investing for more than two years.
우리는 2년 넘게 투자해왔습니다 .
Development is very slow.
개발이 매우 느립니다.
The money invested did not yield the slightest profit.
투자한 돈은 조금도 이익을 얻지 못합니다.
After I saw it,
그것을 본 후,
The number of people living with this rare disease nationwide
전국적으로 이 희귀병 환자 수
Only thirty thousand people remained.
단지 30,000명만 더 있으면 됩니다.
Although our drug has already been IPO,
우리 의약품이 IPO 되었지만,
Where does the profit come from?
이익은 어디서 나올까?
The return on investment is too low.
이 투자 수익률은 너무 낮습니다.
Manager Chen.
첸 매니저.
What is the purpose of Jiehui Company?
Jiehui 회사의 목적은 무엇입니까?
Our profit target for this year
올해 수익 목표
It should be double what it was last year.
작년보다 두 배는 되어야 한다.
Jika HDQ39
지카 HDQ39
Can cure Huntington's disease,
헌팅턴병을 치료할 수 있으며,
It is definitely a major event that caused an uproar in the global medical community.
이는 분명 세계 의료계를 뒤흔드는 중대한 사건이 될 것이다 .
This could kick-start Jiehui's plans for an initial public offering.
이는 Jiehui의 IPO 계획을 시작할 수 있습니다.
Any small amount of money lost by the patient
환자에게 손실된 소액의 돈
Can be withdrawn from the stock market.
주식시장에서 회수할 수 있다 .
Don't just look at the little money in front of you.
눈앞에 있는 작은 돈만 바라보지 마세요 .
correct.
옳은.
Mr. Du's vision is broader.
Du 씨의 견해는 더 넓습니다.
I'm the one who lacks consideration.
나는 배려심이 부족한 사람이다.
If so, I would immediately go and urge the finance department.
그렇다면 즉시 재무부에 가서 촉구하겠습니다.
OK
좋은.
grandfather.
할아버지.
This is the medicinal wine my mother gave you .
이것은 우리 어머니가 주신 약주이다 .
grandfather.
할아버지.
This is Jiehui’s financial report last year.
이것은 Jiehui의 작년 재무 보고서입니다.
Last year, Jiehui totaled
작년에 Jiehui는 총
Introducing 12 categories of medical devices.
12종의 의료기기를 소개합니다.
In terms of scientific research...
과학적인 연구 측면에서...
This Clivia
이 Clivia miniata
No flowers either.
또한 꽃이 피지 않습니다.
grandfather.
할아버지.
Clivia doesn't like water.
Clivia miniata는 물을 좋아하지 않습니다.
Just water once a week.
일주일에 한 번씩만 물을 주세요.
It causes the buds to split.
꽃봉오리가 갈라지는 원인이 될 수 있습니다 .
grandfather,
할아버지,
You poured too much water.
물을 너무 많이 붓고 있습니다.
So that’s it, yes.
알고보니 그렇군요, 네.
Jiehui ini
지에후이이니
Even though it was founded after I retired,
비록 제가 은퇴한 후에 창업했지만,
But I founded this company
하지만 내가 이 회사를 설립했어요
don't want more
더 이상 아무것도 원하지 않는다
Sold some useful patents I owned .
내가 가지고 있던 몇 가지 유용한 특허를 팔았습니다 .
If it weren't for three years ago
3년 전만 아니었으면
You 've wanted to take over the company since you were a kid,
당신은 회사를 인수하고 싶어해서 자랐어요 .
There will be no such development.
또한 이런 종류의 발전 도 없을 것입니다 .
Because the company has been handed over to you,
회사를 귀하에게 양도했기 때문에
There are some things you don't need to tell me.
나에게 말할 필요가 없는 것들이 있습니다 .
up to you.
스스로 결정하십시오.
Thank you, grandpa.
고마워요, 할아버지.
It's getting late, go home and rest.
시간도 늦었으니 집에 가서 쉬세요.
Oh yes. Take away the medicinal wine.
바로 이거 야. 약용주를 가져가세요.
What matters is that people come.
중요한 것은 사람들이 온다는 것이다.
Zheng.
정.
able.
할 수 있다.
It’s been over a year since you went to Lakaya.
당신은 라카야에 온 지 1년이 넘었습니다.
Are you satisfied with that place?
아직 그 곳을 본 것에 만족하시나요 ?
If so, then go home.
그렇다면 집에 가십시오.
I know, Grandpa.
알아요, 할아버지.
[Lakaya]
[라카야]
This aid is still available for two months.
이번 지원은 아직 2개월 남았습니다.
Once the time is right,
일단 시간이 되면,
I will go home.
나는 집에 갈 것이다.
OK
좋은.
Grandpa is waiting for you.
할아버지가 당신을 기다리고 계십니다.
You have to take care of your health.
건강을 돌봐야합니다.
Grandpa is the same, take good care of your body.
할아버지도 건강 잘 챙기세요.
See you later.
그럼 나중에 보자.
Until it was discovered.
발견될 때까지.
[Kota Jinhai]
[코타진하이]
Mother
어머니
You're home, right?
집에 계시죠?
how?
어떻게?
Today, I will report the company’s situation to my grandfather.
오늘은 할아버지께 회사 상황을 보고하면서
Did grandpa praise you?
할아버지가 칭찬해 주셨나요?
During your three years as CEO,
CEO로 재직한 3년 동안,
Jiehui profit growth rate
Jiehui의 이익 성장률
is the highest
가장 높다
Across pharmaceutical companies.
제약회사 전반에 걸쳐
Grandpa said,
할아버지가 말씀하셨다.
You must use red Ganoderma lucidum or purple Ganoderma lucidum to make wine.
와인을 만들려면 빨간색이나 보라색 영지버섯을 사용해야 하는데 ,
Not black reishi.
흑영지 아님.
The effect of soaking black Ganoderma lucidum is not as good as eating mushrooms.
흑영지 불려서 먹는 효과는 버섯을 먹는 것만큼 좋지 않습니다.
Mother
어머니
You don't have to bother doing this next time.
다음 번에는 이 작업을 다시 수행할 필요가 없습니다 .
My hands were split when I washed Ganoderma lucidum last time.
지난번 영지버섯을 씻을 때 손이 갈라졌습니다.
grandfather
할아버지
I can take care of it.
내가 처리할 수 있어요.
It's important that you take care of yourself
중요한 것은 자신을 돌보는 것입니다.
And dad's health, that's enough.
그리고 아빠의 건강이면 충분해요.
what are you saying?
무슨 얘기를 하는 건가요?
This is all my best intention.
이 모든 것은 나의 좋은 의도입니다.
After your grandfather retired,
할아버지가 퇴직하신 후,
He likes to collect medicinal wine and the like.
그는 약용 포도주 와 다른 것들을 수집하는 것을 좋아합니다.
If it weren't for him not letting me enter the old house
그 사람이 나를 낡은 집에 들어가지 못하게 하지 않았다면
Do I need to ask you to get it for me?
내가 당신한테 그걸 가져가달라고 부탁해야 합니까 ?
Dad, I'm back.
아빠, 나 집에 왔어요.
Arrive home already?
이미 집에 있나요?
Your mother said your company's annual report is good.
당신 어머니는 당신 회사의 연례 보고서가 꽤 좋다고 말씀하셨어요.
very good.
매우 좋은.
Thank you dad.
고마워요 아빠.
Such beautiful hands,
너무나 아름다운 한 쌍의 손,
Not holding a scalpel.
메스를 잡지 않고.
Why does it grow on your body?
왜 몸에서 자라나요?
This is very unfortunate.
매우 불행한 일입니다.
Pharmaceutical companies can both cure diseases and save lives.
제약회사는 질병을 치료할 수도 있고 사람을 구할 수도 있습니다.
Oh yes.
바로 이거 야.
Your brother's term of service is coming to an end.
네 동생의 임기가 끝나가는구나.
Have you called him?
그 사람한테 전화했어?
Did he say when he planned to come home?
그가 언제 집에 올 계획 인지 말했나요 ?
You and Yun are my sons, Du Yongsong.
당신과 Yunzheng은 내 아들 Du Yongsong입니다.
We are a family.
우리는 한 가족입니다.
To be proactive, one should be the proactive person.
주도권을 말하고 싶다면 주도권을 쥐는 사람이 되어야 합니다.
You should pay attention to him too.
당신 도 그 사람에게주의를 기울여야합니다.
You're a big brother, right?
당신은 큰 형이죠, 그렇죠?
It’s not like you don’t know Yunzheng’s character.
윤정의 성격을 모르는 것은 아닙니다.
When will he come home?
그 사람은 언제 집에 오나요?
Who will tell Yun Cheng?
누가 윤청에게 말하겠습니까?
He can't even see your WeChat.
그는 당신의 WeChat도 보지 못합니다.
Searching in Cloud City,
윤청이 찾아보니
Isn’t it also wasteful?
그것도 낭비 아냐?
Dad, Mom, I still have a project book to read.
아빠, 엄마, 아직 봐야 할 프로젝트 책이 있어요 .
I'll go up first.
내가 먼저 올라갈게.
Go to bed early and don't stay up late.
일찍 쉬고 밤늦게 일하지 마세요.
You should also go to bed early.
여러분도 일찍 쉬세요.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
I love you for a long time.
나는 오랫동안 당신을 좋아했습니다.
Do you want to date me?
나랑 데이트할래?
accept!
수용하다!
[Library] Accepted!
[도서관] 수락하세요!
why go
왜 가?
What a pity.
정말 부끄러운 일입니다.
[Wen Ran]
[웬란]
♪The night clock continues to tick♪
♪시계는 밤에도 계속 똑딱거리고 있어요♪
♪The noise slowly replaced the silence♪
♪소동이 천천히 침묵을 대신했습니다♪
♪We are performing a meeting script♪
♪ 회의 대본을 연기하고 있습니다 ♪
♪The night is filled with rainbows♪
♪밤에는 무지개가 흩뿌려진다♪
♪With the wind blowing across the desert♪
♪ 사막에 부는 바람과 함께 ♪
♪All this is our testimony♪
♪그 모든 것이 우리의 증인이었어♪
♪Who doesn’t feel lost in confusion? ♪
♪혼란 속에서 길을 잃지 않는 사람은 누구일까요 ?♪
♪Find one among billions of possibilities♪
♪ 수억 개의 가능성 중 하나를 찾아서 ♪
♪Trapped in a city called destiny ♪
♪운명이라는 도시에 갇혀 ♪
♪However, let’s chase stars♪
♪하지만 여전히 별을 쫓고 있어요♪
♪Don't worry, people will lose the direction of what I love♪
♪걱정하지 마세요. 사람들은 내가 좋아하는 방향을 잃어버리니까요♪
♪Hold a glass of wine to warm your lonely soul♪
♪ 외로운 영혼을 따뜻하게 해주는 와인잔을 들고 ♪
♪Let me hug your scars♪
♪네 상처를 안아줄게♪
♪You shine like a star♪
♪당신은 별처럼 밝게 빛나네요♪
♪Sparkle when you are alone♪
♪외로울 때 반짝반짝♪
♪The night clock continues to tick♪
♪시계는 밤에도 계속 똑딱거리고 있어요♪
♪The noise slowly replaced the silence♪
♪소동이 천천히 침묵을 대신했습니다♪
♪We are performing a meeting script♪
♪ 회의 대본을 연기하고 있습니다 ♪
♪The night is filled with rainbows♪
♪밤에는 무지개가 흩뿌려진다♪
♪With the wind blowing across the desert♪
♪ 사막에 부는 바람과 함께 ♪
♪All this is our testimony♪
♪그 모든 것이 우리의 증인이었어♪
♪Who doesn’t feel lost in confusion? ♪
♪혼란 속에서 길을 잃지 않는 사람은 누구일까요 ?♪
♪Find one among billions of possibilities♪
♪ 수억 개의 가능성 중 하나를 찾아서 ♪
♪Trapped in a city called destiny ♪
♪운명이라는 도시에 갇혀 ♪
♪However, let’s chase stars♪
♪하지만 여전히 별을 쫓고 있어요♪
♪Don't worry, people will lose the direction of what I love♪
♪걱정하지 마세요. 사람들은 내가 좋아하는 방향을 잃어버리니까요♪
♪Hold a glass of wine to warm your lonely soul♪
♪ 외로운 영혼을 따뜻하게 해주는 와인잔을 들고 ♪
♪Let me hug your scars♪
♪네 상처를 안아줄게♪
♪You shine like a star♪
♪당신은 별처럼 밝게 빛나네요♪
♪Sparkle when you are alone♪
♪외로울 때 반짝반짝♪